

# **Carlie Berry**

Austin, TX | carlie.berry@yahoo.com | (361) 331-2395 www.linkedin.com/in/carlie-b-127326168/
Portfolio - https://carlieb889.github.io/CarlieBWorks/

## **Professional Summary**

UX / UI Designer with medical coding and billing experience. I gained professional strength going up against big insurance companies fighting for patient's maximum rights and benefits. Recognized by the Donna Lowrey award for going above and beyond my job description, two years in a row from Ernest Health, Inc.

I made the decision to complete the UX/UI Bootcamp at the University of Texas because I believed combining my coding knowledge with my love of design, gaming, and development was the right path to take. My passion for building responsive web designs, and capability to never forget who I am designing for allows me to create user-friendly products excelling in UX/UI Design.

#### **Skills**

- Texas Notary exp 12-10-2022
- Agile Project Management
- Research & Analyzing Data
- Storyboarding
- Prototyping
- Wireframing
- User Flows
- User Experience Design
- User Interface Design

- Invision, Figma, XD, Webflow
- Design Systems
- User Testing & Interviews
- HTML, CSS, JavaScript
- Bootstrap
- Developer Handoff
- Presentations & Communication
- Time Management
- Problem Solving

## **Work History**

#### UX Designer | Kuper Sotheby's Intl Realty | Aug 2018 - Current

Working closely in an agile environment with users, marketing, developers, and stakeholders to improve the real estate platform created by KSIR, Brokerage Engine. User Testing, Wireframing, Prototyping, and Presenting designs and iterations.

### Business Office Specialist | Children's Cardiology Associates | Dec 2015 - Aug 2018

Insurance Verification and Obtaining medical authorizations, Medical Billing and Coding

#### Admissions Specialist | Corpus Christi Rehabilitation Hospital | Oct 2013 – Dec 2015

Facilitating all patient referrals, hospitals admissions, insurance verification and authorizations, and patient discharge plans

#### **Education**

UX|UI Design Bootcamp, University of Texas